tfpc.in 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy – TFPC

## Who we are

Our website address is: https://tfpc.in

welcomes you. We value your privacy, and want you to know what information we collect and what we do with it.

Information Collected by tfpc.in  
You can visit/surf tfpc.in without providing any personal information. However, if you choose to avail of certain services on our website, you shall be required to provide certain information for the registration and/or access to such services/web pages. Such information may include, without limitation, your name, email address, contact address, mobile/telephone number(s), sex, age, occupation, interests, financial information, content, IP address, standard web log information and such other information as may be required for your interaction with the services.

Information Provided to tfpc.in  
tfpc.in features certain areas where we ask you to provide information to us.

Communications with Us:  
We have features where you can submit information to us (such as when contact us, Advertising with us, with a question or problem related to the service). We will retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Who we share your data with

We do not share your personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our service to you, all of which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. Also, entities into which our company is merged, or to which our assets, site or operations have been transferred, will be able to use your personal information under the terms of this privacy policy. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. You should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit your information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission. We may share (provide and receive) with others certain aggregate service information, which is not personally identifiable. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information (such as your email address). We may use aggregate demographic information about our audience in order to improve our service, for marketing purposes and/or industry reporting purposes.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Additional information

Links:  
We may display links to other sites within tfpc.in. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

Downloads:  
We do link to other web sites which might support downloads. We are not responsible for the downloadable materials that are present in these websites. We are also not responsible for the legalities and privacy policy binding the downloadable materials of these websites. We are also not responsible for the legalities and privacy policy binding these downloads in the websites that our visitors refer to in our forums and discussions. Downloads referred to in this privacy policy can be videos, images, software, games and any application files.

» Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
» Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
» Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://networkadvertising.org.

Changes in this Privacy Statement  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and such other places we deem appropriate so that you are updated about the manner we collect information, what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
